Any entertainment there?
All right. Here we go!
1999, the year of Joey.
그래, 좋았어
1999년, 조이의 해
We're very happy for you.
좋겠다
What's the matter?
왜 그래?
We wanted to kiss at midnight,
but nobody else will, so....
우린 자정에 키스하고 싶은데
다른 사람들은 안 할 거잖아
All right, I'll take care of it.
알았어
- 나한테 맡겨
- 안 돼!
It's 30 seconds to midnight,
what are you gonna do?
조이, 30초 남았는데
어떻게 하겠다고?
날 못 믿어?
Will you just trust me?
33, 32...
Thirty-three, 32, 31
- 로스...
- 31
Who are you kissing at midnight?
Rachel or Phoebe?
자정에 누구랑 키스할래?
레이첼이야, 피비야
뭐?
누구한테든 해야지
여동생은 안 되고
You can't kiss your sister.
-Who's gonna kiss my sister?
-Chandler.
내 동생은 누구랑 하는데?
- 챈들러
- 맙소사...
Oh, man! Really?
야, 누가 낫겠어
나? 챈들러?
Would you rather
have me or him kiss her?
- 예리한 지적이다
- 그럼
That's a good point.
Since I have that whole history
with Rachel, I guess Phoebe.
레이첼하고는 사연이 많아서
피비를 택해야겠다
- 좋았어
- 그래
Phoebe! Listen.
Ross wants to kiss you at midnight.
피비, 나 좀 봐
로스가 자정에 너한테
키스하고 싶대
So obvious.
Why doesn't he just ask?
당연하지
직접 물어보라고 해
-Rach! I'm gonna kiss you at midnight.
-What?
- 레이첼, 자정에 너한테 키스할래
- 뭐?
You can't kiss Ross.
You got the history.
누가 됐든 키스는 해야지
로스랑은 좀 껄끄럽잖아
So?
그래서?
누가 좋겠어
나? 챈들러?
-Would you prefer me or Chandler?
-Good point.
- 예리한 지적이다
- 그럼
Three, two, one!
셋, 둘, 하나!
Happy New Year!
새해 복 많이 받아!
-Happy New Year.
- 새해 복 많이 받아
- 새해 복 많이 받아, 피비
- 너도
-Happy New Year.
-You too.
Happy New Year, Joey.
새해 복 많이 받아, 조이
So that do anything for you?
아무 느낌 없나?
The One with
All the Resolutions
아무래도 올해는
액땜을 해야겠다
You know what?
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and say "No divorces in '99!"
99년에 이혼은 없다!
But your divorce isn't final yet.
이혼이 마무리된 건 아니잖아
Just the one divorce in '99!
- 99년에 이혼은 딱 한 번만!
- 그렇지!
올해는 행복하게 살 거야
스스로 행복을 찾겠어
I am gonna be happy this year.
I am gonna make myself happy.
우리 그냥 나갈까?
Do you want us to leave the room?
Every day I am gonna do one thing
I have never done before.
여태껏 한 번도 안 해본 걸
매일 하나씩 할 거야
That is my New Year's resolution.
그게 내 새해 계획이라고
그거 정말 멋지다
That's a good one!
난 여객기 파일럿 될 거야
Mine is to pilot a commercial jet.
Now you only have to find
a planeload of people...
그것도 멋지긴 한데
올해는 꼭 비행기 사고로
죽겠다는 사람들부터 찾아라
...whose resolution is
to plummet to their deaths.
넌 친구를 놀리지 않는 걸
새해 계획으로 삼아라
Maybe your resolution should be
not to make fun of your friends.
특히 널 비행기에 태워
유럽으로 데려다줄 친구는
Especially the ones who might
fly you to Europe for free.
She has a better chance
of flying up your nose...
너 그 버릇 고치는 것보다
피비 날개 돋는 게 더 쉽겠다
...than you do of
not making fun of us.
우리들 놀리지 않고 한 해를
보내면 내가 50달러 주겠어
I'll bet $50 you can't go the year
without making fun of us.
아니다, 일주일로 하자
Better yet, a week.
내기를 받아들이지
I'll take that bet, my friend.
Paying me the $50 can be...
나한테 50달러 주는 것도
그 날의 새로운 일이 될 거야
...the "new thing you do" that day.
And it starts right now!
당장 시작하자고
My New Year's resolution is
to learn how to play guitar.
내 새해 계획은
기타를 배우는 거야
정말? 갑자기 왜?
Really? How come?
내가 이력서에 나열한
특기사항들 있잖아
You know those special skills
I have listed on my resume?
I would love it
if one of those was true.
그 중 하나 정도는
사실이었으면 해
Want me to teach you?
I'm great.
내가 가르쳐줄까?
나 잘 가르치는데
그래? 누굴 또 가르쳤는데
Really?
Who have you taught?
내가 날 가르쳤는데
아주 맘에 들어
Well, I taught me. And I loved me.
그럼 좋지, 고맙다
That'd be great!
Yeah, thanks, Phoebe.
올해는 나도 지나치게
깔끔 떨지 않기로 했어
My resolution is to be less obsessed
with being neat and clean.
진짜?
Really?
안 돼!
Or something else.
다른 걸로 해야겠다
Look. Blaire forgot her glasses.
이런, 블레어가
안경을 두고 갔네
She'll need these to keep an eye
on that boyfriend.
남자친구 감시하려면
이게 필요할 텐데
Who, from what I hear,
needs to keep his stapler...
내가 듣기로는 그 남자
바람기가 여간 아냐
...in his desk drawer,
if you know what I mean!
무슨 뜻인지 알지?
Maybe your resolution
should be to gossip less.
넌 올해부터
남의 험담을 좀 줄여라
What? I don't gossip.
누가 험담을 한다고!
난 우연히 듣거나 알게 된
정보를 전달하는 것 뿐이야
Maybe sometimes I find out things.
Or I hear something
and I pass that information on.
You know, kind of
like a public service.
일종의 공익사업처럼
It doesn't mean I'm a gossip.
Is Ted Koppel a gossip?
그게 무슨 험담이야
테드 코펠도 험담꾼인가?
If Ted Koppel talked about his
coworkers' botched boob jobs, I would.
가슴수술 실패한 동료
얘기를 한다면 그렇지
They were like this!
이렇게 됐단 말이야
Fine, my New Year's resolution
will be not to gossip.
좋아, 알았어
내 새해 계획은
남의 험담 안 하기
쉽지
-It's easy.
-Easy? You have never kept a resolution.
쉬워? 새해 결심
지킨 적 있어?
왜 없어?
-Yes, I have.
-Okay, let's see how you did last year.
그럼 작년에 어땠는지 보자
안 돼, 내 일기 손대지 마
No. No. Not my diary.
You cannot read my diary.
일기야, 올해의 결심은
매일 널 쓰는 거란다
"Dear diary: I'm so excited.
My resolution is to write in you every day.
See you tomorrow."
내일 또 보자
깨끗해
Nothing.
알다시피 작년엔 일이 많았어
You know, not a lot happened last year.
좋아, 이번엔 약속 지킨다
이제 험담 안 할게
All right, I will prove to you that I can keep it
this time. No more gossiping.
나도 중학교 때
I hate gossip. In junior high this girl
said a lot of mean stuff about me...
내 험담을 늘어놓던 계집애
자전거에 불을 질러버렸어
...and I set her bike on fire.
- 뭐라고 했는데?
- 날더러 미쳤대
-Wow, what did she say about you?
-She said I was crazy.
But I guess she got hers.
제대로 본 거지
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
- 그럼 내일 봐요
- 좋아요
I just asked that girl out.
저 여자 만나기로 했다
- 잘했어
- 제법인데?
Nice!
Is that part of
your "new thing" for today?
매일 새로운 걸 하겠다는
새해 결심의 일환인가?
맞아, 보여?
Yes, it is. See?
"Elizabeth...
엘리자베스...
...Hornswoggle"?
혼스워글?
That's right.
그래
Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
엘리자베스 혼스워글
혼... 스워글
You okay, Chandler?
너 괜찮니?
그 이름이 웃겨?
Something funny about that name?
No, I just think
I've heard it somewhere before.
아니, 어디서 들은 이름 같아서
Oh, really? Where?
그래? 어디서?
Somewhere funny, I'll bet.
웃기는 데겠지?
- 안녕, 피비
- 얘들아
Guess what.
나 데이트하기로 했다
엘리자베스 혼스워글이랑
I have a date
with Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
혼스워글...
Oh, this must be killing you!
너 좀 힘들겠다
All right, see you later.
- 나중에 보자
- 그래
뭐 괜찮아
Not really.
- 중간 이름도 있어
- 얘기하지 마
-I haven't told you her middle name yet.
-Well, don't. Just don't.
- 나 간다
- 그래
-See you later.
-See you.
All right, Phoebe,
I am ready for my first lesson.
좋아, 피비
첫 레슨을 시작해보자
그래
No, you don't touch the guitar.
기타는 만지지 마
안 돼, 이거부터 하고
이걸로 들어가야지
First you learn here, then here.
알았어
좋아
Lesson one: Chords.
제1강, 코드...
Now, I don't know
the actual names of the chords.
난 코드 이름을 모르거든
But I made up names for the way
my hand looks while I'm doing them.
그래서 손 모양을 따서
이름을 지었어
됐지?
자, 이건 '곰 발바닥'
So then this is "Bear Claw."
"Turkey Leg"...
그리고 '칠면조 다리'
또 이건 '노파'
...and "Old Lady."
What an interesting approach
to guitar instruction.
흥미로운 기타 강좌
접근법이구나
누구는 웃기겠지만
나한텐 정통으로 보인다
You know, some might find it amusing.
I myself find it regular.
Hey, everybody!
얘들아
Rachel was so good today.
She didn't gossip at all.
레이첼이 하루 종일
험담을 안 했어
I didn't.
Even when I found out
그래, 심지어는...
Let's say I found out
something about someone...
누군가의 뭔가를 알아냈지만
이렇게만 말할게
'그냥 입다물고 있을게'
...and let's just say...
...she's gonna keep it.
피비, 이것 좀 봐
Check this out.
우! '노파'를 확실히 잡았네
You nailed the Old Lady!
I thought I was getting better,
so I stopped by this guitar store
실력이 좀 느는 것 같아서
기타 가게에 들렀는데...
가게에 들어가서
기타를 만졌어?
Did you touch
any of the guitars there?
Did you?
그랬어?
No.
아니
Give me your hands.
손 이리 줘
Strings.
기타 줄
이 손
Pick.
픽
-Do you want to learn to play guitar?
-Yes.
- 정말 기타를 배우고 싶어?
- 그래
그럼 만지지 마!
Then don't touch one!
- 얘들아
- 안녕
- 어서 와라, 벤
- 모니카 고모다
-Hi, Ben.
-Auntie Monica!
Ross is wearing leather pants!
로스 가죽바지 입었다
Does nobody else see
Ross is wearing leather pants?
다들 저 가죽바지 안 보여?
Someone comment on the pants!
뭐라고 한마디해봐
-I think they're very nice.
-I really like them a lot.
괜찮은데?
- 그래, 좋아
- 멋지다
Not what I had in mind.
내 생각은 달라
People like Ross don't wear
these types of pants.
로스 같은 사람은
이런 바지를 안 입어
You see, they're very tight.
보여? 꽉 조이잖아
Maybe there's something in that area?
그 부분을 집중적으로 생각해
- 좋다니까 왜 그래?
- 괜찮은데?
I think they look really good.
어디서 샀어?
Where'd you get them?
오늘도 새로운 게 필요했는데
I needed a new thing for today.
가죽제품 가게 지날 때마다
냄새가 참 좋아서 생각했지
There's this leather store
that always smells so good.
여태 좋은 냄새나는 바지를
입어본 적이 없더라고
And I thought to myself:
"Wow. I've never owned...
...a really good-smelling
pair of pants before."
Oh, come on!
너무들 한다!
What do you think?
솔직히 말해, 어때?
- 끔찍하다
- 망측스러워
You look like a freak.
Awful!
What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거야?
-It's my New Year's resolution.
-To blind my child?
내 새해 계획이야
내 아들 장님 만드는 게?
우리 사진을 많이 찍을 거야
To take pictures of us together.
It's the best resolution.
Everyone can enjoy them.
괜찮은 생각이잖아
사진은 다들 좋아하니까
Everyone will enjoy my music as well.
내 연주도 좋아할 거야
My God, these pants!
I'm burning up.
이런, 바지에 불이 붙었나?
Oh God! She wants to snuggle now?
Is she trying to kill me?
지금 엉겨 붙으면 어쩌자고
화산 곧 폭발하는데
It's like a volcano in here!
-Are you hot?
-No.
- 더워요?
- 아뇨
It must just be me, then.
그럼 나만 그런 거구나
That was just the pants
and the couch.
바지가 소파에 쓸리는 소리예요
Do you mind if I use your bathroom?
화장실 좀 써도 될까요?
-Go ahead.
-Thanks.
- 그래요
- 고마워요
여기가 제일 멋진 장면이에요
My favorite part's coming up!
알았어요
Oh, my God!
엄마야
호랑이
Tiger.
Dragon.
용
Iceberg!
빙산
Joseph, did you even study
at all last night?
조이
밤새 공부한 거 맞아?
Yes, I did!
그래, 공부했어
Then do lceberg.
그럼 빙산 해봐
G-sharp.
G샵
G샵?
G-sharp?
Have you been studying
the real names of the chords?
진짜 코드 이름까지 외웠어?
Have you?
그랬어?
내가 못살아
Oh, my God!
기타는 손도 안 댔어
What? I didn't touch a guitar!
내 교습법을 의심하잖아
But you're questioning my method!
의심하는 게 아냐
확실히 멍청한 짓이지
No, I'm not questioning it.
I'm saying it's stupid!
What?
뭐야?
Thank you.
고마워
다른 학생은 날
멍청하다고 생각 안 해
You know, none of my other student...
...thought I was stupid.
Your other student was you!
그 다른 학생은 너였어!
Well, maybe you just need
to try a little harder!
그래, 조금만 더 노력하면
될 건데 왜 그래?
난 진짜 선생을 만나고 싶어
Maybe I need to try a real teacher!
자, 이걸 봐
Here! Andy Cooper.
He teaches guitar.
앤디 쿠퍼, 기타 선생이야
여기 애들도 같이 있네
There's a picture of him with a kid.
And the kid's got a guitar!
기타까지 들고!
Fine!
좋아!
You learn from
your "qualified instructor."
자격증 있는 선생 찾아가라
But don't come crying
when everyone is sick...
'악당 리로이 브라운'
연주하면 사람들 좋아하겠다
...of hearing you play
"Bad, Bad Leroy Brown"!
마을에서 가장 지독한 악당
Oh, fine. Take his side!
그래, 조이 편들어라
I can't wait to be with you.
빨리 함께 있고 싶어
오빠가 벤 데려가는 대로 갈게
I'll sneak over as soon as I can.
I'll tell Rachel
I'll be doing laundry.
레이첼한테는 몇 시간
빨래한다고 둘러대고
Laundry.
Is that my new nickname?
빨래? 그게 내 별명인가?
아냐
You know what your nickname is,
Mr. Big
알잖아, 자기 별명은...
그렇게 쳐다보지 마
Would you stop looking at me like that?
Phoebe was a terrible teacher.
피비는 엉터리 선생이야
I wasn't learning anything from her
배운 것도 없어, 나라고 좋겠니?
됐다, 똑같은 말 지겨워
Look I feel bad, too
Forget it, we're going around in circles.
들어가 봐
여보세요
Joey, it's Ross.
I need some help.
조이, 나 로스야
좀 도와줘
Chandler's not here.
- 챈들러는 없는데
- 네가 도와줘
You can help me.
좋아
여긴 엘리자베스 집 화장실이야
I'm in Elizabeth's bathroom.
잘했다
Nice!
아냐, 가죽바지가 너무
더워서 벗었는데
No, I got really hot in my pants,
so I took them off.
But they must have shrunk
from the sweat.
땀을 먹어서
바지가 줄어들었는지
Or my legs expanded from the heat.
아니면 내 다리가
열 받아서 부었는지
I can't get them back on, Joey.
I can't!
다시 입을 수가 없다니까
That is quite a situation.
그거 참 절묘한 상황이구나
Do you see any powder?
파우더 같은 거 있어?
Powder! Yeah, I have powder.
그래, 여기 파우더 있다
Good, good.
좋아, 잘됐다
다리에다 좀 뿌려봐
그럼 바지가 들어갈 거야
Sprinkle some on.
It'll absorb moisture.
Then you can get your pants on.
잠깐 기다려 봐
Yeah, hold on.
효과 없다, 오버
They're not coming on, man.
Okay, cut slits in the pants, right?
Then put them back on...
그렇지
바지를 찢어서
다시 입은 후에 나가서
'두 얼굴의 사나이'라고 해
...go out there
and tell her you're the lncredible Hulk.
Chandler's not there?
거기 챈들러 없다고?
그래도 되지만
알았어, 좋아
That would have worked,
but all right, fine.
You see any....
Oh, Vaseline?
혹시 바셀린 있어?
I see lotion. I have lotion.
Will that work?
여기 로션은 있는데
이거라도 될까?
당연하지, 살짝 덮어 줘
Sure, throw some of that on there.
Hold on.
잠깐만
Sounds like it's working.
잘 되나 보네
They're still not coming on, man.
그래도 안 올라온다
로션이랑 파우더가 풀이 됐어
And the lotion and the powder
have made a paste.
Really.
그래?
What color is it?
무슨 색깔인데?
What difference does that make?
그게 무슨 상관이야
If the paste matches the pants,
you can make paste pants...
색깔이 맞으면 풀 먹인
바지라고 하면 되잖아
...and she won't know!
Do you have a minute?
조이, 시간 있니?
Dude, what am l
야, 이제 난...
Rachel's here, so good luck.
Let me know how it goes.
레이첼 왔다, 잘해봐
결과 나오면 알려주고
Joey, I have such a problem.
조이, 문제가 생겼어
Your timing couldn't be better.
타이밍 한번 완벽하다
오늘 불 끄느라 정신 없는데
I'm putting out fires
all over the place.
그래, 알았어
조이, 꼭 할말이 있어
I have got to tell you something.
What is it?
뭔데 그래?
너무 엄청난 일이거든
아무한테도 말하지 마
It's so huge! But promise me.
You cannot tell anyone.
- 됐어, 알고 싶지 않아
- 뭐?
No, no, no!
I don't want to know.
알고 싶을 걸?
대형사건이야
You do want to know.
This is unbelievable!
상관없어
I'm tired of being the guy
who knows all the secrets...
비밀을 담고 사는 거
너무 피곤한 일이더라
...and can't tell anyone.
- 넌 무슨 비밀을 아는데?
- 험담 안 하기로 했잖아
You know secrets?
You're not supposed to gossip!
이건 참을 수가 없어
전화기를 들었는데...
I can't keep this in.
So I pick up the phone
I'm not listening to you!
안 들린다
로스?
You've been in there for a long time.
거기 너무 오래 있었는데
I'm starting to get
kind of freaked out.
걱정되잖아요
All right, I'm coming out.
네, 지금 나가요
Hey, can you turn the lights off?
불 좀 꺼줄래요?
아뇨, 그냥 켜둘래요
Let's just leave the lights on.
Oh, my God!
맙소사
I had a problem.
문제가 좀 있어요
피비?
I can't talk to you. I don't have
a fancy ad in the yellow pages.
전화번호부에 광고도 안 나간
내가 어떻게 너랑 얘길 하겠니
저기...
피비, 그게...
I want to apologize for saying
your method was stupid.
사과하고 싶어
멍청하다고 말한 거
And maybe ask you
to be my teacher again?
혹시 다시 배울 수 있을까?
I promise, I won't touch a guitar
until you say I'm ready.
네가 괜찮다고 할 때까지
기타는 절대 손 안 댈게
You really think I'm ready?
진짜 만져도 돼?
Wow, cool!
와, 신난다
좋아
-Was the chord at least right before
-No.
- 그래도 코드는 제대로...
- 아니
Oh, my God!
내가 미친다
We heard about your pants.
I'm so sorry.
바지 얘기 들었어
이 일을 어째
This year was supposed to be great.
멋진 한 해를 계획했는데
It's only the second day
and I'm a loser...
겨우 이틀만에 맞지도 않는
가죽바지 때문에 푼수 됐어
...with stupid leather pants
that don't even fit!
You're not a loser.
- 넌 푼수 아냐
- 그런 말 마
Look at me!
날 보라고
Hey, look!
오빠, 여기
이걸 봐
Ben drew a picture of you.
벤이 오빠를 그렸어
카우보이잖아
You're a cowboy.
Because of the leather pants?
이 가죽바지 때문에?
벤한테 오빠는 푼수가 아냐
He thinks you're a cowboy,
not a loser. That's something.
아빠를 카우보이로 생각한다고
- 그래, 얼마나 좋아
- 안녕, 파트너?
-lt really is something.
-Howdy, partner.
Maybe I should get another pair.
다른 걸 사볼까?
You know, they had some...
옆에 술이 주렁주렁
달린 것도 있던데
...with fringe all down the sides.
Phoebe, you may know this.
You know strange things.
피비? 넌 알 거야
희한한 걸 많이 아니까
뇌의 끓는점이 몇 도지?
What is the boiling point of brain?
I used to know this.
알았었는데
벤한테 잘 자라고 해야지
I'm gonna go kiss Ben good night.
I can't believe he thinks
I'm a cowboy.
날 카우보이로 생각하다니
I would make a good cowboy.
나도 카우보이 할 수 있어
여긴 대충 정리됐으니까
난 가서 빨래나 할래
Now that everything's wrapped up,
I'll do my laundry.
Yeah, me too.
If this shirt is dirty.
나도, 셔츠가 더럽다면
그렇군
I'm going to the airport.
난 공항에 가야 돼
If I hang around there
long enough...
기다리다 보면 조종사 없이
뜨는 비행기도 있을 거야
...someone's bound to leave
a plane unattended.
-Good luck, honey.
-Bye.
- 잘해봐
- 안녕
저기, 조이?
아까 하려던 얘기 있지?
Remember that thing
I was gonna tell you about?
싫어, 싫어...
I won't tell you.
But if you found out on your own...
얘기 안 할 거야
하지만 네가 알아낸다면
...that would be okay
and we could talk about it.
그땐 서로 얘기해도
괜찮은 거지?
Well, then it wouldn't be a secret.
So that would be okay.
그럼 비밀이 아니다?
그렇다면 괜찮지, 좋아
그래, 좋아
Would you mind going
into Chandler's bedroom...
챈들러 방에 가서 내가
빌려준 책 좀 갖다줄래?
...and getting that book
he borrowed from me?
Now? You want me
to go over there now?
지금? 지금 가라고?
-Do you know something?
-Do you?
- 너 뭐 아니?
- 넌 뭐 알아?
-I might know something.
-I might too.
- 나 뭐 좀 알아
- 나도 좀 알지
-What do you know?
-You tell me first.
- 넌 뭘 아는데?
- 네가 아는 것부터 말해
- 난 말 못 해
- 나도 말 못 해
-I can't.
-Then I can't.
Okay, fine.
그럼 좋아
You don't know.
넌 몰라
I'll walk into his bedroom
and see the thing...
직접 챈들러 방에 가서
내가 알고 있는 게
사실인지 확인해볼래
...I think I know is actually
the thing I think I know!
-You know!
-And you know!
- 너도 알아?
- 너도 알고?
Yeah, I know!
그래, 알아
Chandler and Monica?
Oh, this is unbelievable!
챈들러랑 모니카가?
믿을 수가 없네
-How long have you known?
-Too long!
- 언제부터 알았는데?
- 너무 오래됐어
세상에! 입이 가려워서
환장할 뻔했어
I've been dying to talk
to someone about this!
You can't say anything to anybody.
They're so weird about that.
- 명심해
- 그래
아무 말도 하지 마
너무 이상한 사건이야
피비!
It's raining.
비 온다
비행은 힘들겠어
I don't like to fly in the rain.
I am gonna go for a walk
in the rain.
- 난 빗속에서 산책할 거야
- 나도
Me too.
That's weird.
거 참 묘하네
I bet they're doing it.
뭔가 진행 중이야
좋아, 더는 안 돼
이제 못 참겠어
Okay, look.
I can't take it anymore.
네가 이겼다
됐지? 받아
So you win. Okay?
Here.
피비, 비행기를 몰아?
Flying a jet?
Make it a spaceship...
우주선이 낫지 않을까?
지구로 돌아올 수 있도록
...so you can get back
to your home planet!
로스, 톰 존스가 전화했더라
바지 돌려달라고
Phone call for you. Tom Jones.
He wants his pants back!
그리고 혼스워글?
'프래글 락' 캐릭터를 만나?
And Hornswoggle? What, are you dating
a character from Fraggle Rock?